embassyhomepage.com 2019-07-03

# High Commission in London

PRIVACY POLICY OF EMBASSYHOMEPAGE.COM WEBSITE

How We Protect Your Privacy  
This website privacy policy tells you how we collect, use, and protect your personal information. By visiting our website Embassyhomepage.com., you accept and agree to the terms and conditions of this website privacy policy. In particular, you consent to our collection and use of your personal information as described in this website privacy policy. 

Minors  
We do not provide services or sell products to children. If you are below the age of 18, you may use our website only with the permission and active involvement of a parent or legal guardian. If you are a minor, please do not provide us or other website visitors with any personal information. 

This Policy Is Part Of Our Terms And Conditions Of Use  
Our website privacy policy is a part of, and subject to, our website’s terms and conditions of use. You may view these terms and conditions on our website. 

The type of information we collect from you and interest-based advertising.   
Like most places on the Internet, simply by visiting our website you automatically tell us certain information. This includes basic information such as your IP address, when you visited, the website from where you came prior to visiting us, the website where you go when you leave our website, your computer’s operating system, and the type of web browser that you are using. Our website automatically records this basic information about you. 

And like many other websites, we may use cookies. In plain English, this means information that our website’s server transfers to your computer. This information can be used to track your session on our website. Cookies may also be used to customize our website content for you as an individual. If you are using one of the common internet web browsers, you can set up your browser to either let you know when you receive a cookie or to deny cookie access to your computer. 

We may also collect any data that you provide us by posting it at our website or by sending to us via email. You can always choose not to provide us with information. However, if you do withhold information, we may deny you access to some or all of our website’s services and features. 

Some transactions between you and our website may involve payment by credit card, debit card, checks, money orders, and/or third party online payment services. In such transactions, we will collect information related to the transaction as part of the course of doing business with you, including your billing address, telephone number, and other information related to the transaction. 

What We Do With Your Information  
This privacy notice tells you what to expect when this website Embassyhomepage.com and parent company [Business Web Hosting Company Pty Ltd](http://www.businesswebhostingcompany.com/) collects personal information. It applies to information we collect about: 

** > visitors to our websites**  
** > complainants and other individuals in relation to a data protection or freedom of information complaint or enquiry**  
** > people who use our services, eg who subscribe to our newsletter or request a publication from us**  
** > people who notify under the Data Protection Act**  
** > job applicants and our current and former employees**

We use your information to operate our website’s business activities. For example, we may use this data to contact you about changes to our website, new products and services, special offers, resolve disputes, troubleshoot issues, and enforce our website’s terms and conditions. 

As a general rule, we will not give your data to third parties without your permission. However, there are some important exceptions to this rule that are described in the following paragraphs. 

We may, in our sole discretion, provide information about you to law enforcement or other government officials for purposes of fraud investigations, alleged intellectual property infringement, or any other suspected illegal activity or matters that may expose us to legal liability. 

Although we do not disclose individually identifiable information, we may disclose aggregate data about our website’s visitors to advertisers or other third parties for marketing and promotional purposes. 

From time to time, we may use third party suppliers to provide services on our website. If a supplier wants to collect information about you, you will be notified. However, you will never be required to give information to a third party supplier. We restrict the way third party suppliers can use your information. They are not allowed to sell or give your information to others. 

Interest-Based Advertising, Remarketing, and Dynamic Ad Serving  
_Interest-Based Advertising_

When you visit our website, you may view advertisements posted on the site by Google or other companies. These advertising companies may collect information about you while you are visiting this website and other websites. They may use this data to show you advertisements on this website and elsewhere on the Internet about products and services you might like. 

This website does not collect the information or control the content of the advertisements that you will see. You may be able to opt out of such advertising. To find out more about Google privacy policies and its DoubleClick DART cookie used to generate interest-based advertising, go to <http://www.google.com/privacy/ads/>. 

_Remarketing_

This website may use a remarketing tag to advertise online. This means that Google and other third-party vendors may show our ads to you on sites across the Internet. These third-party vendors, including Google, may use cookies to serve ads to you based upon your past visits to our website. 

If you would like to opt out of Google’s use of cookies, you can visit the company’s Ad Preferences Manager at <https://www.google.com/ads/preferences/>. 

In the alternative, you can opt out of the use of cookies by third-party vendors by going to the Network Advertising Initiative’s opt-out page located at <http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp>. 

_Dynamic Ad Serving_

Our website may use Google’s Dynamic Ad Serving feature. This ad serving feature uses the Teracent cookie. You can opt-out of the Teracent cookie at the Teracent opt-out page located at <http://www.teracent.com/about-us/opt-out>. 

_DoubleClick Remarketing Pixels_

Our website may use DoubleClick’s remarketing pixels. If you would like to opt out of DoubleClick’s use of cookies, you can visit the DoubleClick opt-out page at <https://www.google.com/settings/ads/onweb#display_optout>. 

In the alternative, you can opt out of use of cookies by third-party vendors by going to the Network Advertising Initiative’s opt-out page located at <http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp>. 

Your use of this website without opting out means that you understand and agree to data collection to provide you with interest-based advertising. 

User Names And Passwords  
Your access to parts of our website may be protected by a user name and a password. Do not give your password to anyone. If you enter a section of our website that requires a password, you should log out when you leave. As a safety precaution, you should also close out of your web browser completely and re-open it before viewing other parts of the Internet. 

Your Use Of Information And Unsolicited Commercial Email  
If you obtain personally identifiable information about another website user, you are not allowed to disclose this information to anyone else without the consent of the user and our consent too. 

We hate junk email (spam). Information you obtain from our website about us or other site users cannot be used by you or others to send unsolicited commercial email or to send unsolicited commercial communications via our website’s posting or other communication systems. 

Your Voluntary Disclosure Of Information To Third Parties Who Are Not Our Suppliers  
You may choose to provide personal information to website visitors or other third parties who are not our suppliers. Please use caution when doing so. The privacy policies and customs of these third parties determine what is done with your information. 

Autoresponders  
We may use autoresponders to communicate with you by email. To protect your privacy, we use a verified opt-in system for such communications and you can always opt-out of such communications using the links contained in each autoresponder message. If you have difficulties opting out, you may contact us by sending an email to legaldept[at]businesswebhostingcompany.com, or sending us mail to the address listed below. 

Visitors to our websites  
When someone visits Embassyhomepage.com we collect standard internet log information and details of visitor behaviour patterns. We do this to find out things such as the number of visitors to the various parts of the site. We collect this information in a way which does not identify anyone. We do not make any attempt to find out the identities of those visiting any of our websites including Embassyhomepage.com. We will not associate any data gathered from this site with any personally identifying information from any source. If we do want to collect personally identifiable information through our website, we will be up front about this. We will make it clear when we collect personal information and will explain what we intend to do with it. 

**Use of cookies by Embassyhomepage.com**  
Cookies are small text files that are placed on your computer by websites that you visit. They are widely used in order to make websites work, or work more efficiently, as well as to provide information to the owners of the site. 

The table below explains the cookies we use and why. 

**Cookie** : Embassyhomepage.com site cookie acceptance  
**Name** : Embassyhomepage.com cookies accepted  
**Purpose** : This cookie is used to record if a user has accepted the use of cookies on the Embassyhomepage.com website.  
**More Information** : To withdraw your consent after accepting this cookie, delete the Embassyhomepage.comCookiesAccepted cookie. Find out how at [www.aboutcookies.org](http://www.aboutcookies.org/)

**Cookie** : Google Analytics  
**Name** : _utma, _utmb, _utmc and _utmz  
**Purpose** : These cookies are used to collect information about how visitors use our site, which we use to help improve it. The cookies collect information in an anonymous form, including the number of visitors to the site, where visitors have come to the site from and the pages they visited.  
**More Information** : [Click here for an overview of privacy at Google](http://www.google.com/intl/en_uk/analytics/privacyoverview.html)

**Cookie** : Google Adsense and DoubleClick  
**Name** : PREF. SID. HSID, lbcs, __gads, id, _drt_, FLC, NID and exchange_uid  
**Purpose** : These cookies are used to make advertising more engaging to users and more valuable to publishers and advertisers. Some common applications of cookies are to select advertising based on what�s relevant to a user; to improve reporting on campaign performance; and to avoid showing ads the user has already seen.  
**More Information** : [Click here for an overview of privacy policy at Google Adsense and DoubleClick](http://www.google.com/policies/privacy/cookies/types/)

**Cookie** : Trade Doubler  
**Name** : TD_UNIQUE_IMP, TD_POOL, TD_PIC, TD_ANTEC, BT, TD_EH, TradedoublerGUID, OPT_OUT and RET  
**Purpose** : To serve and monitor advertisement views, rotate, track, limit and target ads to users with a specific browsing behaviour, monitor past clicks on ads and to allow user to disable cookie based tracking or targeting for the browser that the user is using.  
**More Information** : [Click here for an overview of privacy policy at Trade Doubler](http://www.tradedoubler.com/uk-en/privacy-policy/)

**Cookie** : CJ (Commission Junction)  
**Name** : S, SESS, LCLK, PBLK  
**Purpose** : S is used to recognise when a user first interacts with an advertisement and later acts on that advertisement by reaching a certain page on one of our advertiser’s websites. Later used to match this activity with post-view or post-click conversions. SESS is used to for the timestamp of the most recent user click, by advertiser and also used to determine when a browser session starts. LCLK is used for The timestamp of the most recent user click, by advertiser and also used for used for click to sale correlations. PBLK is used to identify the website id and timestamp of the most recent click, by advertiser as well as used to redirect to a publisher supplied url, if that publisher is deemed to have driven the most recent click  
**More Information** : [Click here for an overview of privacy policy at CJ.com (Commission Junction)](http://uk.cj.com/legal/cookie-policy)

Most web browsers allow some control of most cookies through the browser settings. To find out more about cookies, including how to see what cookies have been set and how to manage and delete them, visit [www.aboutcookies.org](http://www.aboutcookies.org/) or [www.allaboutcookies.org](http://www.allaboutcookies.org/). 

To opt out of being tracked by Google Analytics across all websites visit <http://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout>. 

**Purchases:** Embassyhomepage.com does not sell you products, but directs you to sites that do. These sites may store information such as your name and address and credit card details. They may operate their own privacy policies. 

YouTube cookies  
We embed videos from our official YouTube channel using YouTube�s privacy-enhanced mode. This mode may set cookies on your computer once you click on the YouTube video player, but YouTube will not store personally-identifiable cookie information for playbacks of embedded videos using the privacy-enhanced mode. To find out more please visit YouTube�s embedding videos information page. 

Search engine  
The search engine on our website is designed to be as powerful and easy to use as the popular search engine Google. The search is made possible by a piece of hardware (a search �appliance�) supplied by Google that is plugged into our server and continuously indexes the content on our site. All search requests are handled by the appliance and the information is not passed on to any third party, including Google. 

**E-newsletters and Auto Responders**  
We use a third party provider, AWeber, to deliver our e-newsletters and email auto responder services. We gather statistics around email opening and clicks using industry standard technologies including clear gifs to help us monitor and improve our e-newsletters and email marketings. For more information, please see AWeber’s privacy notice. 

People who call our call centres  
When you call the Embassyhomepage.com’s call centre we collect Calling Line Identification (CLI) information. We use this information to help improve its efficiency and effectiveness.

Our call centre phone line also offers a translation service for customers when English is not their first language, this is provided by a third party company. The company that provides this service does not retain any information from the calls or record them. 

People who make a complaint to us  
When we receive a complaint from a person we make up a file containing the details of the complaint. This normally contains the identity of the complainant and any other individuals involved in the complaint. 

We will only use the personal information we collect to process the complaint and to check on the level of service we provide. We do compile and publish statistics showing information like the number of complaints we receive, but not in a form which identifies anyone. 

We usually have to disclose the complainant’s identity to whoever the complaint is about. This is inevitable where, for example, the accuracy of a person’s record is in dispute. If a complainant does not want information identifying him or her to be disclosed, we will try to respect that. However, it may not be possible to handle a complaint on an anonymous basis. 

We will keep personal information contained in complaint files in line with our retention policy. This means that information relating to a complaint may be retained for up to four years from closure. It will be retained in a secure environment and access to it will be restricted according to the ‘need to know’ principle. 

Similarly, where enquiries are submitted to us we will only use the information supplied to us to deal with the enquiry and any subsequent issues and to check on the level of service we provide. 

When we take enforcement action against someone, we may publish the identity of the defendant in our Annual Report or elsewhere. Usually we do not, identify any complainants unless the details have already been made public. 

People who use Embassyhomepage.com services  
The Embassyhomepage.com offers various services to the public. We use a third party to deal with some publication requests, but they are only allowed to use the information to send out the publications. 

We have to hold the details of the people who have requested the service in order to provide it. However, we only use these details to provide the service the person has requested and for other closely related purposes. For example, we might use information about people who have requested a publication to carry out a survey to find out if they are happy with the level of service they received. When people do subscribe to our services, they can cancel their subscription at any time and are given an easy way of doing this. 

People who ‘notify’ under the Data Protection Act 1998  
We are required by law to ‘notify’ certain specified information to the Information Commissioner in each country we operate. This may contain personal information. 

When we are asked to fill in their notification forms to the Information Commissioner, we need to provide the contact details of a relevant member of staff. 

**Job applicants, current and former employees of Embassyhomepage.com or its parent company**   
When individuals apply to work at Embassyhomepage.com or its parent company, we will only use the information they supply to us to process their application and to monitor recruitment statistics. Where we want to disclose information to a third party, for example where we want to take up a reference or obtain a ‘disclosure’ from the Criminal Records Bureau we will not do so without informing them beforehand unless the disclosure is required by law. 

Personal information about unsuccessful candidates will be held for 12 months after the recruitment exercise has been completed, it will then be destroyed or deleted. We retain de-personalised statistical information about applicants to help inform our recruitment activities, but no individuals are identifiable from that data. 

Once a person has taken up employment with the Embassyhomepage.com or its parent company, we will compile a file relating to their employment. The information contained in this will be kept secure and will only be used for purposes directly relevant to that person�s employment. Once their employment with Embassyhomepage.com or its parent company has ended, we will retain the file in accordance with the requirements of our retention schedule and then delete it. 

Access to personal information  
Embassyhomepage.com tries to be as open as it can be in terms of giving people access to their personal information. Individuals can find out if we hold any personal information by making a ‘subject access request’ under the latest Data Protection Act. If we do hold information about you we will:   
give you a description of it;  
tell you why we are holding it;  
tell you who it could be disclosed to; and  
let you have a copy of the information in an intelligible form.

To make a request to the Embassyhomepage.com for any personal information we may hold you need to put the request in writing addressing it to our Information Governance department, or writing to the address provided below. 

If you agree, we will try to deal with your request informally, for example by providing you with the specific information you need over the telephone. 

If we do hold information about you, you can ask us to correct any mistakes by, once again, contacting the Information Governance department. 

Disclosure of personal information  
In many circumstances we will not disclose personal data without consent. However when we investigate a complaint, for example, we will need to share personal information with the organisation concerned and with other relevant bodies. Further information is available in our Information Charter about the factors we shall consider when deciding whether information should be disclosed. 

You can also get further information on:  
agreements we have with other organisations for sharing information;  
circumstances where we can pass on personal data without consent for example, to prevent and detect crime and to produce anonymised statistics;  
our instructions to staff on how to collect, use and delete personal data; and  
how we check that the information we hold is accurate and up to date. 

Links to other websites  
This privacy notice does not cover the links within this site linking to other websites. We encourage you to read the privacy statements on the other websites you visit. Please read the Embassyhomepage.com&rsqo;s reciprocal linking policy for more information. 

Policy Changes

The terms of this policy may change from time to time. If such changes are made, we will notify you by a notice posted either on our website’s home page or on this page of the changes that have been made. If you disagree with the changes that have been made, please contact us (by email, using a website contact form, or in writing by mail), and any changes made to this policy will not apply to information we have collected from you prior to making the changes. 

If you are concerned about the topic covered by this website privacy policy, you should read it each time before you use our website. 

Questions or Concerns  
Any questions or concerns about this website privacy policy should be brought to our attention by sending an email to legaldept[at]businesswebhostingcompany.com and providing us with information relating to your concern. 

You may also mail your concerns to us at the following address: 

Business Web Hosting Company Pty Ltd  
Baulkham Hills Business Centre  
PO Box 7051  
Baulkham Hills  
New South Wales 2153  
Australia. 

California Privacy Rights  
If you are a California resident and our customer, Cal. Civ. Code � 1798.83 permits you to request certain information about our disclosure of personal information to third parties for their direct marketing purposes. To request this information, please send an email to legaldept[at]businesswebhostingcompany.com or write us at the following address: 

Business Web Hosting Company Pty Ltd  
Baulkham Hills Business Centre  
PO Box 7051  
Baulkham Hills  
New South Wales 2153  
Australia. 

This website privacy policy was last updated on September 16, 2013. 

This document is Copyright � 2008-2013 Law Office of Michael E. Young PLLC, and licensed for use by the owner of this website at Embassyhomepage.com. All Rights Reserved. No portion of this document may be copied or used by anyone other than the licensee without the express written permission of the copyright owner.
